Yeah!
Unbelievable!
The Knights
take the lead
despite the massive
gap in strength.
The score is now 17-7.
What the hell
are you doing?
This game's
almost over.
You stop that
son of a bitch
or you're fucking fired.
You said you
could beat this guy.
If you lose this game,
you'll be scrubbing fucking toilets.
I have no other options.
I can't win.
Fucking useless.
Every fucking
one of you,
useless.
Nice, nice!
Oh my God!
Nobody thought
it could happen.
Nobody wanted
it to, besides me,
but guess what?
The Knights have won
the NFL Championship!
You can sleep
well tonight, Mom!
Ted! I know you
won't be sleeping.
You'll be doing a lot of other things tonight!
And enjoy, my friend.
You deserve it!
The NFL Champions,
the Knights!
Hey!
Where you going, West?
Don't you
remember our bet?